coinmedia.co 2018-08-30

# CoinMedia.Co - Bitcoin Advertising Network.

### CoinMedia Internet service privacy policy of the provided information

This Privacy Policy of the provided information (hereinafter referred to as the "Policy") has been approved by the administration of CoinMedia (hereinafter referred to as the Administration, the Company), whose website is on the Internet at coinmedia.co (hereinafter referred to as "Service" and the "Website") and applies to all users of the Service (hereinafter referred to as the "Users"). 

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and process your information, including personal data, in connection with the use of the Service and in connection with the access to them. 

Use of the Service means the User's unconditional consent to this Policy and the conditions of processing the information provided by the User. In case of disagreement with these conditions, the User should refrain from using the Service. 

### 1\. Types of information provided by the Users.

1.1. The User, using the Service, including passing the registration procedure, sending messages, letters and otherwise interacting with the Company, provides the Company some information and data that are personal. 

1.2. We collect the following information: 

1.2.1. The information you provide us. 

1.2.1.1. The information required to use the Service. We request and collect the following personal data when you use the Service. This information is necessary for us to properly fulfill the contractual obligations to you, and also to comply with the requirements of the law. Some services may not be available without this information. Registration information. When registering an Account, we request certain information in order to create an Account and provide access to it. Interaction with the Company. When you communicate with the Company, we collect information about your communication, as well as other information that you provide (for example, your requests to the support team); 

1.2.1.2. Information that you provide to us on your own initiative. By choice you can provide us with other personal data in order to improve interaction with the Service. 

1.2.2. Information that we automatically collect when you use the Service. The data that is automatically transmitted when viewing advertising units and when visiting pages with statistical script of the system ("pixel"): • IP address • information from cookie • information about the browser (or other program that provides accesses to viewing the advertising) • access time • address of the page with the advertising unit • referrer (address of the previous page) You can refuse your personal information being collected by changing the appropriate settings in your browser. 

### 2\. Objectives of collecting and processing of information provided by the Users.

2.1. The Service uses the information it collects for the following purposes: 

2.1.1. Identification of the User in the framework of the agreements and contracts with the Service, provision of personal services to the User on the Service Site (execution of agreements and contracts with the User); 

2.1.2. Display of the advertising that is more relevant and interesting for the User, targeting of advertising materials by geographical criteria, interests and other parameters. 

2.2. The User at any time can change (update, supplement) the information provided in clause 2.1.1. hereof. To do this, the User must be authorized on the Site and introduce necessary changes into the personal account. 

2.3. The information provided in clause 1.2.2. hereof is absolutely anonymous and is used exclusively to improve the quality of the Service's services and marketing purposes. The User at any time can refuse their personal information being collected by using appropriate settings of the browser, which allows to refuse installation of cookies (possibly, as a result, the User will not be able to use all the features of the Service Site fully). If the User does not refuse to use cookie, the Service will send cookie when the User accesses the Service Site. 

### 3\. Conditions of processing and storing information provided by the User.

3.1. The Service shall take all reasonable technical and organizational measures to protect the information provided by the Users from unauthorized or accidental access to it, from destruction, modification, blocking, copying, distribution, as well as from other improper actions of third parties with it. 

3.2. The Users understand and agree that the Service cannot provide guarantees of absolute protection of the information provided by Users and guarantee absolute safety of communications between the Users and the Service. The User is aware and agrees that the information input by them can be used by search engines or other automated services and in other ways. 

3.3. The User is solely responsible for keeping own login / password secret from third parties and promptly changing the password and / or contacting the Service support service in case of loss or disclosure of the password. 

3.4. With respect to the User's personal information, its confidentiality is maintained, except for the cases of voluntary provision by the User of personal information for general access to an unlimited number of persons. 

### 4\. Refusal of data collection.

4.1. When displaying advertising, we do not collect personal data of the Users, such as name, surname, email, postal address or phone number. We collect anonymous data (such as IP address, city, country, etc.), which enable us to segment users to optimize advertising campaigns, so that we can more accurately select the content of the banner message for each specific user. 

4.2. To provide our services, we use technologies such as cookies. In any case, you can always change your browser's settings to disable cookies and prevent data collection if you have any concerns about protecting your personal data. Read the documentation for your browser to learn how to block cookies. 

### 5\. Rights of the User.

To exercise any of the rights described in this section, the User must send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) Please note that we can ask you to verify your identity before fulfilling your request. 

5.1. Access and Control of own information. The User has the right to access all personal information and data stored in the Company's databases and also to change it using the Account settings. The User is solely responsible for maintaining the relevance of own personal data. 

5.2. Correction of inaccuracies or incompleteness of data. The information and data can be changed (updated, supplemented) by the User at any time. You have the right to request from us to correct incorrect or incomplete personal data, if you cannot change it in your Account independently. 

5.3. Storage and deletion of data. In general, we store your personal data for the period necessary to properly fulfill the contractual obligations to you and to comply with the requirements of applicable law. If you want to revoke the permission to use your information to provide you the access to the services of the Service, you can send a request for the deletion of your personal data and the Account. 

### 6\. Changing of the Policy. Applicable Legislation.

6.1. The Service has the right to introduce changes to this Policy. The new version of the Policy shall come into force from the moment of its posting, unless otherwise provided by the new edition of the Policy. The current version is always available at <https://coinmedia.co/policy.html>. If you disagree with the updated Policy, you can delete your account. If you do not delete the account and continue to use the Service, you thereby confirm your acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy. 

### 7\. Feedback.

7.1. Any suggestions or questions about this Policy should be reported to the Service Support at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Date of effect – May 25, 2018.
